<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Classic</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Classic</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Most Universal tool of man</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/post/2024/07/18/most-universal-tool-of-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/post/2024/07/18/most-universal-tool-of-man/</guid>
      <description>Wheel yes, wheel&#xA;One of the Man&amp;rsquo;s greatest invention of all time. Our very basic movement will somehow have wheel in our life. It has been our day-to-day essential one for work.&#xA;Let us go back to man&amp;rsquo;s early history. At first man tame animals for his use. The first animal to be tamed was the dog. It watch and warned the master approcaching danger&#xA;Man soon discovered that pack of dogs could pull a fairly heavy load.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What makes me happy</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/post/2024/07/14/what-makes-me-happy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/post/2024/07/14/what-makes-me-happy/</guid>
      <description>What make me happy?? Sridhar: I want my life to be full of great moments&#xA;Also me: Great moments exists inside the ordinary moments. continues to enjoy the moment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I need a Network monitoring tool</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/post/2024/07/05/why-i-need-a-network-monitoring-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/post/2024/07/05/why-i-need-a-network-monitoring-tool/</guid>
      <description>Why I need to monitor the network modern understanding of network monitoring needs additional approaches.&#xA;a network traffic analysis Network monitoring collects data from servers, routers, firewalls, switches, etc. The goal is to detect intrusions into networks, identify vulnerabilities, and prevent attacks. Network monitoring can be performed manually or automatically.&#xA;some open source tools are: Nagios Zabbix Cacti Zenoss Munin Netflow Wireshark The best features of Network Monitoring Software are:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What should I consume in online</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/post/2024/07/04/what-should-i-consume-in-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/post/2024/07/04/what-should-i-consume-in-online/</guid>
      <description>Substance consuming Problem?? Yes, a substance abuse problem. We are consuming a lot of information irrelevant to our willness but that will eventually get used to us and also will comfort us making us not realize that it sucks our time and that procastination that done is by video content majorly. The one thing i noticed in me that, i have been consuming a lot of reels when i see my digital welbeing dashboard and realizing that these are my peak time which i should stipulate for upskilling myself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why People are apolitical</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/post/2024/07/04/why-people-are-apolitical/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/post/2024/07/04/why-people-are-apolitical/</guid>
      <description> This question always strikes me, whenever people over here are apolitical&#xA;they are comfortable with the current political climate people doesn&amp;rsquo;t care about how society is functioning or they may be extremely priveledged they will throw money and think that their problem disappear and not the society problem. they don&amp;rsquo;t care about the social issues around them becasue it doesn&amp;rsquo;t affect them. they may be willfully ignorant and they avoid forming opinion because it will burst their precious priveledged bubble </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why People are apolitical</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/post/2024/07/04/why-people-are-apolitical/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/post/2024/07/04/why-people-are-apolitical/</guid>
      <description>I love the journey as its not all about the desitnation and its also about our travel in our jouney.&#xA;When we board our train, We were having a nice chitchat about some random things that we usually talks about.&#xA;The last time we were returning from Kozhikode to Pondy, we were witnessing the aweful large mountains throughtout the way near palakad and all were enjoying the moment in our train journey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Setting up a custom dns server</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/post/2024/07/03/setting-up-a-custom-dns-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/post/2024/07/03/setting-up-a-custom-dns-server/</guid>
      <description>links to proceed with:&#xA;https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-set-up-my-own-DNS-server https://opensource.com/article/17/4/build-your-own-name-server https://meshnet.nordvpn.com/how-to/security/how-to-set-up-your-own-dns-server https://www.howtogeek.com/devops/how-to-run-your-own-dns-server-on-your-local-network/ https://www.pcmag.com/how-to/how-and-why-to-change-your-dns-server https://www.ninjaone.com/blog/how-to-configure-a-dns-server/ https://meshnet.nordvpn.com/how-to/security/protect-network-with-adguard-home Also read about dnsmasq - a free software tool&#xA;https://stevessmarthomeguide.com/home-network-dns-dnsmasq/ https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/Dnsmasq </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I love Linux</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/post/2024/07/03/why-i-love-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/post/2024/07/03/why-i-love-linux/</guid>
      <description>Why I started using it?? I started using it because I found it cool and I wanted to be so too. It is also less of a pain in the butt compared to Windows. I got used to the Linux way of doing things and I find the way Linux does many things like&#xA;It just works as the way I want the way I install programs the complete freedom of it the transparent nature of it all more appealing than Windows’ way of doing things.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Guide (modified)</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/post/2018/08/30/markdown-guide-modified/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/post/2018/08/30/markdown-guide-modified/</guid>
      <description>An h1 header Paragraphs are separated by a blank line.&#xA;2nd paragraph. Italic, bold, and monospace. Itemized lists look like:&#xA;this one that one the other one Note that &amp;mdash; not considering the asterisk &amp;mdash; the actual text content starts at 4-columns in.&#xA;Block quotes are written like so.&#xA;They can span multiple paragraphs, if you like.&#xA;Use 3 dashes for an em-dash. Use 2 dashes for ranges (ex., &amp;ldquo;it&amp;rsquo;s all in chapters 12&amp;ndash;14&amp;rdquo;).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacker with Bullhorn</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/post/2012/04/23/hacker-with-horn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/post/2012/04/23/hacker-with-horn/</guid>
      <description>Hacker with bullhorn: &amp;ldquo;Save your money! Accept one of our free tanks! It is invulnerable, and can drive across rocks and swamps at ninety miles an hour while getting a hundred miles to the gallon!&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Prospective station wagon buyer: &amp;ldquo;I know what you say is true&amp;hellip;but&amp;hellip;er&amp;hellip;I don&amp;rsquo;t know how to maintain a tank!&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Bullhorn: &amp;ldquo;You don&amp;rsquo;t know how to maintain a station wagon either!&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Buyer: &amp;ldquo;But this dealership has mechanics on staff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Command Line Awesomeness</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/post/2012/03/12/command-line-awesomeness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/post/2012/03/12/command-line-awesomeness/</guid>
      <description>This crud is called HTML (HyperText Markup Language) and it is basically a very simple programming language instructing your web browser how to draw a page on a screen. Anyone can learn HTML and many people do. The important thing is that no matter what splendid multimedia web pages they might represent, HTML files are just telegrams.&#xA;When Ronald Reagan was a radio announcer, he used to call baseball games by reading the terse descriptions that trickled in over the telegraph wire and were printed out on a paper tape.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Juicy Code</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/post/2012/01/23/juicy-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/post/2012/01/23/juicy-code/</guid>
      <description>Check out this JUICY! code:&#xA;def with_value_from_database(value) self.class.from_database(name, value, type) end def with_cast_value(value) self.class.with_cast_value(name, value, type) end def with_type(type) if changed_in_place? with_value_from_user(value).with_type(type) else self.class.new(name, value_before_type_cast, type, original_attribute) end end </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
